[{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980316348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":13438,"timeElapsed":156955},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980322915,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":6567,"timeElapsed":163522},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980327401,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":4484,"timeElapsed":168008},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980331209,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3807,"timeElapsed":171816},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980338171,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":6961,"timeElapsed":178778},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980342765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4593,"timeElapsed":183372},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980349017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":6251,"timeElapsed":189624},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980354899,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":5881,"timeElapsed":195506},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980360031,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5131,"timeElapsed":200638},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980372161,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":10643,"timeElapsed":212768},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980377931,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":5769,"timeElapsed":218538},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980382915,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":4983,"timeElapsed":223522},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980385335,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2419,"timeElapsed":225942},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980388315,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2979,"timeElapsed":228922},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980394117,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5801,"timeElapsed":234724},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980398251,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":4133,"timeElapsed":238858},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980402567,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4315,"timeElapsed":243174},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980405073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2505,"timeElapsed":245680},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980413791,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":7115,"timeElapsed":254398},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980417879,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4087,"timeElapsed":258486},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980420985,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3105,"timeElapsed":261592},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980424251,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":3265,"timeElapsed":264858},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980427257,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3005,"timeElapsed":267864},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980434285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":7027,"timeElapsed":274892},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980437055,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2769,"timeElapsed":277662},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980442213,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":5157,"timeElapsed":282820},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980444681,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2467,"timeElapsed":285288},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980453799,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":7559,"timeElapsed":294406},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980456927,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3127,"timeElapsed":297534},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980460687,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":3759,"timeElapsed":301294},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980464007,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":3319,"timeElapsed":304614},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980466843,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2835,"timeElapsed":307450},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980471521,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4677,"timeElapsed":312128},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980473713,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2191,"timeElapsed":314320},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980479575,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":5861,"timeElapsed":320182},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980484515,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4939,"timeElapsed":325122},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980489911,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5395,"timeElapsed":330518},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980496989,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":5807,"timeElapsed":337596},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980499397,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":2407,"timeElapsed":340004},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980502657,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3259,"timeElapsed":343264},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980505406,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2748,"timeElapsed":346013},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980508249,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2842,"timeElapsed":348856},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980514049,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":5799,"timeElapsed":354656},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980516765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2715,"timeElapsed":357372},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980522713,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":5947,"timeElapsed":363320},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980525869,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":3155,"timeElapsed":366476},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980534259,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":7167,"timeElapsed":374866},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980537691,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3431,"timeElapsed":378298},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980540499,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2807,"timeElapsed":381106},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980543943,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":3443,"timeElapsed":384550},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980548843,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":4899,"timeElapsed":389450},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980555937,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":7093,"timeElapsed":396544},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980558733,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2795,"timeElapsed":399340},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980562245,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3511,"timeElapsed":402852},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980565023,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2777,"timeElapsed":405630},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980852917,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":286639,"timeElapsed":693524},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980856621,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3703,"timeElapsed":697228},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980860783,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4161,"timeElapsed":701390},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980862995,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2211,"timeElapsed":703602},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980865837,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2841,"timeElapsed":706444},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980870073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4235,"timeElapsed":710680},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980872645,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2571,"timeElapsed":713252},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980876185,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":3539,"timeElapsed":716792},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980878769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2583,"timeElapsed":719376},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980882661,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3891,"timeElapsed":723268},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980891243,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":7065,"timeElapsed":731850},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980893877,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2633,"timeElapsed":734484},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980896497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2619,"timeElapsed":737104},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980898857,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2359,"timeElapsed":739464},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980902415,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3557,"timeElapsed":743022},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980906029,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":3613,"timeElapsed":746636},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980908447,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2417,"timeElapsed":749054},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980912717,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":4269,"timeElapsed":753324},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980916299,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":3581,"timeElapsed":756906},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980983003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":65525,"timeElapsed":823610},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980985901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2897,"timeElapsed":826508},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980988823,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2921,"timeElapsed":829430},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980991601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2777,"timeElapsed":832208},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980994467,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2865,"timeElapsed":835074},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980997803,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3335,"timeElapsed":838410},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981000875,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3071,"timeElapsed":841482},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981004245,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3369,"timeElapsed":844852},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981006499,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2253,"timeElapsed":847106},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981016271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":8561,"timeElapsed":856878},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981019359,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":3087,"timeElapsed":859966},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981022713,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3353,"timeElapsed":863320},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981025431,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2717,"timeElapsed":866038},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981029037,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3605,"timeElapsed":869644},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981032357,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3319,"timeElapsed":872964},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981035023,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2665,"timeElapsed":875630},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981039683,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4659,"timeElapsed":880290},{"subjectID":"mfbzd3nkbw","prolificID":"5ffb8c5b60571908f3ac19fa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b237493e4f2f58ec8e2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981042335,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2651,"timeElapsed":882942}]